Yamagata Prefecture.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's so good!
I'm Natsume Nakayama and Miku Nishizaki from Ocha-no-Mama.
Yes, yes.
So, we're here to make a kilo of tea.
Yes, sir.
Everyone, please look this way.
This is the big Osho.
Do you know where we are?
Yes, of course.
This is Yamagata Prefecture.
You made it!
You are here.
This chess piece.
Yes.
Yamagata Prefecture is very famous.
I'd like to go sightseeing in Yamagata and eat a lot of things that go well with tea.
I want to enjoy eating a lot of food that goes well with tea.
I'm off to Yamagata!
So, without further ado...
I'm in front of Tendou station in Tendou city.
I didn't expect the shape of the post box!
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's in the shape of a Japanese chessboard.
It's a bit shocking.
I wonder if I can go there.
I see it, I see it!
This is the red post in the shape of a chessboard.
Can you see it?
Tendou, the town of hot springs, the king's move for your trip... oh, my God... Shogi...
There's so much love for Shogi, even just at the station, and they're celebrating Sota Fujii's 8th championship there, too.
Natsume-san, I don't know much about Shogi, but my parents watch the broadcasts, and every time Sota Fujii takes a break during a game, the snacks he eats become famous, so every time...
I see. Well, we're here now, and it's like this.
The more we walk, the more we find something.
We have to look for tea cakes again.
Imoni and cherry blossoms are famous too.
I looked it up and found lots of famous ones.
So I hope we can try some of the famous ones.
I think so! I'm off!
Bye bye!
So I was taken to a house... but I can't grasp what it looks like because it's only a piece of bread.
Let's go ahead and take a look... but it's really neat... what's this?
I can feel the nature.
I heard they stopped making cherry tomatoes, but they don't seem to have any...
I can see them now.
I feel like cute kids are showing up.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, this one.
They're here, they're here.
They're here.
What's this?
They were cherries.
Yah, I'm here to pick cherries.
I'm so happy.
You know, it's just the right thing to do.
There seems to be a place where there are lots of cherries.
So we headed there, and here they are!
They are all growing up to become beautiful cherries.
Let's eat!
Okay, let's try a little.
I'm going to use this one.
She's going to hold the tree and turn it up.
Then you can take a beautiful picture.
Okay, I'll eat the food.
Please eat.
Yum!
It's really sweet! You want some, too, Miku?
I don't know! There's so much over there, I'd like to go through it!
This is so good! Isn't this great?
Wait, this is great! This store is awesome!
Is it good? I'll get it!
Take the branch and swoop it up!
Nice!
It's going to work! And now, let's eat!
This is amazing!
It melts in your mouth!
It tastes wonderful!
The best cherries ever!
Well, from now on, we'll be preying on a lot of cherries.
We're going to be preying on a lot of cherries.
I think we're eating a lot.
Let's go to Nakayama!
Here we go!
Oh, but it's hard to do this with one hand!
Oh, I got it!
Ta-da!
Bon appétit!
Aaah!
Oh my gosh!
Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Keep it coming.
I like this one.
It's so beautiful.
Bon appétit.
Oh, my God.
This is too good.
Keep it coming!
It's the reflection of the cherry blossoms.
I can see them.
Look how smooth they are!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It's too good!
It's so red.
Ta-da!
Bon appétit!
I really don't know how to eat cherries!
Maybe I should go to the back!
Oh my god!
They're so beautiful!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Miku, look!
Three.
Or three sisters. They're pink.
Delicious!
Oh, man, but, you know, the sweetness seems to vary from tree to tree.
Oh, no!
I'm out!
I got three!
Ta-da! I got a breath too!
Bon appétit!
Wow.
Seriously, this is the best food I've ever had!
Hoo!
Yum!
Look at this.
This one's amazing, too.
Yum!
Delicious!
Amazing, everyone!
Bright red cherry blossoms.
So many!
But I think it's very rare to eat sakurambo in this season.
This precious...
Oh, I said tanks.
I want to eat a lot of them!
They are really delicious!
I'm sure you'll be happy too!
If you come to Yamagata Prefecture, please go cherry picking!
They are the most delicious!
This is a cute video of what cherries look like!
Can you see how beautiful the colors are?
Oh, it's in focus, just like my eyes!
I got my eyes here, too.
I want you to use this.
The color is so beautiful.
I don't know how many I've eaten.
I'm going to eat these.
It's very difficult to do.
Go ahead.
Go!
Let me go!
All right, here we go.
It's really good. It spreads slowly.
It's really good, it spreads slowly.
It's too good, really good.
It's too good.
It's so good, I can't stop. I probably ate 20 of them.
Three, you see? It's a reflection. It's too beautiful, too shiny.
Bon appétit! Oh, my God, I'll have some.
Oh, it's sweet. High sugar content.
It's too good.
It's too delicious.
Look at this... it's so red.
Can you see it?
See, it's easier to see when you look like this.
I don't know when this video was uploaded.
But if it's cherry season, you should definitely come!
When you come to Yamagata Prefecture
By the way, we are not in the middle of cherry season
Not exactly in the middle of the season
about this time.
I'll make some comments.
About this much
Yes, sir.
I'll put it on when it's about the same size as it is now.
Oh, it's delicious! It's really delicious!
I'm pretty full.
So fast!
The color is totally different.
Look!
This one's really red.
But this one's not so red.
If you're going to go that far...
I'd like to have this red one.
Oh, I ate one. Twins.
So cute!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Delicious!
Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
I don't know what to do.
Where should I take it?
Here.
Oh, let's do this.
Let's put her on top.
Like this, like this.
You can take it off.
It's delicious.
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Oh, my God.
Oh, okay.
Shall we harvest the cherry blossoms first?
I'm pretty visual.
Me too.
You do?
A red-hot, pantywaisted girl.
This one's good, isn't she?
Oh, yeah, that's a good one.
Let's go with her.
I, I, I, I, I, I, I think I'll pick her.
That's a good one. I'm not sure about that one.
Oh, you were lost?
Yeah, it's bad around here.
Go!
Yee-ha hah!
Okay, I got it.
You want the front or the back?
Can I pick one?
Yeah. - Okay.
Okay, I'll go ahead.
Oh, okay.
This one.
Here you go. - Okay.
It's bright red. My blush red paklang.
I'd like to have some.
It's so delicious.
It's like a sizzling sensation in your mouth.
I couldn't get it out of my mouth in an instant.
Only those who have tasted it can understand how wonderful it is.
Please go to Yamagatake!
You're getting good at food reporting, aren't you?
Who are you looking at?
Okay, Mr. Yamagatake!
I'll go to Nakayama next.
Here you go.
Look at this bright red cherry blossom!
I chose her because it was love at first sight.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It's gone.
Open your mouths, everyone!
Bon appétit!
That's right.
Of course it's all sweet.
But there are two kinds of sweet.
There are two kinds of sweet.
I just ate a very sweet one.
It's really delicious!
I want some too, so can I have some?
Me too.
Bye bye!
Well, that was fun!
It was so much fun to choose the sweetness and eat it by myself!
It was the first time in my life to eat freshly caught and freshly cooked food right then and there.
It was great!
I can't close it, what should I do?
It's fine, it's fine.
Close the crocs and stuff.
I know, the tops of the cucumbers are all healthy and they just pop right out...
Thank you for watching.
Shift this girl, shift the formation,
It worked.
It's all done.
It was my first time to make sakura mogari.
Me too.
Yes, I had been strawberry picking at a local farm,
But this was the first time for me to try sakura mogari,
I was happy to be able to do it in Yamagata, which is famous for it.
It was a great memory for me.
I hope you will all go too.
I hope you will go too.
Bye bye. Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
We, we are the happiness we create.
We, we, we, Eva Drijop, all the way. Countless japasilas shining in our hearts.
Thank you for the food.